Can I put Andal in?
アンダル入れていい?
I want to play Andal.
アンダルしたい
Oh, that's amazing.
おーすごい
Ah, that's amazing.
あーすごいよ
Does Andal feel good?
アンダル気持ちいいの?
It feels good.
気持ちいいよ
Andal feels really good.
アンダルめっちゃ気持ちいいよ
If you do it too hard, it will break, so be gentle.
アンダル激しくするとね、切れちゃうから優しくがいいんだ
Andal is seriously dangerous just by tapping it in the back.
アンダルって奥トントンするだけでマジでヤバい
Ah, it feels good.
あー気持ちいい
It feels good to erase the hole.
消す穴気持ちいい
The front hole doesn't catch either.
前の穴も引っかけない
this?
これ?
It became sticky.
ベチャベチャになっちゃいました
Wait a minute, now.
ちょっと待ってね、今ね
My computer got wet.
パソコン濡れちゃったからね
Stay hydrated.
水分補給する
I want to change my pet sheets right now.
ちょっと今、ペットシーツも変えたいな
Sorry.
ごめんね
Please wait a moment.
ちょっと待っててね
I'll come back with a ponytail.
ポニーテールにして戻ってくるから
Please wait a moment.
ちょっと待っててください
Which of the three areas do you feel the most?
3箇所だとどこが一番感じる?
Hmm, 7 pieces.
う ーん、7個
parentheses
かっこ
good.
いい
Warm pet sheets.
ペ ットシーツあったかい
Is it impossible to appear in Andal?
アンダルに出るのは無理?
It seems impossible.
無理そうだな
I've never done it before.
やったことないしな
Wait, I'll be right back, so don't go missing.
待ってね、すぐ戻ってくるからいなくなんないでね
Yes, sorry to have kept you waiting.
はい、お待たせしました
I'm home
ただいま
ー.
ー
Right now.
ただ いまー
Cuper time.
クパータイム
Would you like to have a cuppa time?
クパータイムしますか
What do you think?
どうですか?
appear?
見える?
Okay, hurry up.
おケケ、はやかけ
That's right.
そうなんだよね
Oh, open your fingers.
あ、手指開いて
No longer.
さなくなった
I guess so.
そうかな
Blur your fingers.
手指をぼかして
More up-close.
もっとドアップで
More up?
もっとドアップ?
Are you a little nervous when you see them jumping around?
ぴょんぴょんを見て、ちょっとはやかけなの?
It's disgusting.
気持ち悪いね
Did you put it in Chen Qing's hole?
チェンチンの穴に入れたの?
secret.
内緒
I'll leave it to your imagination.
想像におまかせします
Include your face too.
顔も入れて
appear?
見える?
Lift your butt up.
お尻を持ち上げてください
Andal is opening up a lot.
アンダルがすごい開いちゃってる
I want to include Chen Ching.
チェンチン入れたいね
Even if you open it all the way, you can't go any further.
全開まで開いても、これ以上は無理
It's difficult to get out of the hole.
穴の奥も出て難しいんだよね
Yotsunbai.
よつんばい
Do you want to sleep?
よつんばいする?
Yotsunbai.
よつんばい
Ya Bakune?
や ばくね?
Spread it out.
広げて
My butt jiggles.
お尻プルプル
Yes, my butt is jiggling.
そう、お尻プルプルなのよ、私
Hey hey, let's make it a hole again?
ねえねえ、また穴にしよう?
Let's make it a hole.
穴にしようよ
Let's do it.
しようしよう
Are you going to cry?
泣いちゃうよ?
Also.
また
I feel horny.
ムラムラする
It's been a tough week.
1週間大変だったわ
Did everyone make holes?
みんな穴にしてましたか?
It got sticky again.
ベッチャベチャにした、また
I'm kind of buzzing.
なんかピョンピョンしてる
amazing.
すごい
What is this, a ninja?
何これ、忍者?
Awesome.
すげえ
I can't use my fingers, so I'll do this.
指だと私いけないから、これでやる
I really can't go without a phone.
電話じゃないと私マジでいけないんだよね
Let's jerk off.
シコシコでシコシコしよう
Ah, it feels good.
あー、気持ちいい
I held back until I cried in the south.
南で泣くまで我慢した
TRUE?
本当?
Great.
えらい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
This phone is definitely the best.
やっぱこの電話最強
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
Show me how much you squirt.
思いっきり潮吹きを見せて
Because I blew a lot earlier.
さっきめっちゃ吹いちゃったからな
Stop for a second.
ちょっとやめて
Don't stop breathing your pussy.
マンコの呼吸とかやめないで
I laughed.
笑っちゃった
It's really interesting though.
めっちゃ面白いんだけど
amazing.
すごい
I was really looking at it just now.
めっちゃ見てたね、今
Did you see it?
見てた?
Properly.
ちゃんと
That's amazing.
すごいよ
So messed up.
めっちゃめちゃ
I'm going to torture you, why?
拷職するぞ、どうして
like this.
こう
Things are getting serious.
大変なことになってきました
That's terrible.
やばいね
It's like Bawa.
バワったいね
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
My butt is already in trouble.
もうお尻が大変なことになっちゃった
Just change it once.
ちょっと一回交換ね
This is dangerous.
これがやばい
Sorry, I'm not gone.
ごめんね、いなくなってないよ
I'm there though
いるんだけど
hey.
ね
Will it come out again?
また 出るかな?
I think it will go away if you drink tea.
お茶飲めば出ると思うよ
Is it a little dark?
ちょっと暗いかな?
More up?
もっとアップ?
It's already bad.
もうやばいね
It's covered in koseko.
コセっこまみれてる
It's already hard.
もう大変だ
The construction has gotten really big.
作りがすごい大きくなっちゃった
No, that's amazing.
いや、すごいね
How many days has it been since?
何日ぶり?
I do it as a woman pretty much every day.
割と毎日女にしてるんだけどね
The only time I can blow it so hard is when I'm doing this stream.
こんなに思いっきり吹くのはこの配信やってる時だけだから
I'm happy.
うれしいよ
I want to find it, but I'm afraid of the camera.
見つけたいけどね、カメラが焦がれる
I really like this.
これめっちゃ好き
I wonder how long it will take to replace it if it does.
やられるといつまで交換しちゃうかも
It's crazy, it's really perverted.
やばいよね、本当に変態だよね
I'll have some tea.
ちょっとお茶飲むよ
I only have a little tea left.
もうお茶が少ししかない
Tea is delicious.
お茶うま
Are you back?
戻ってきた?
yes.
そう
general
普
If you drink this tea, you will be able to play.
通 にこのお茶飲むと 吹ける
With tea.
お茶で
The tea makes me want to go to the bathroom.
なんかお茶で トイレ行きたくなるから
I can only show you a little bit of my face.
顔はちょっとずつしか見せれないよ
No more.
もうダメ
Anyone who hasn't gone yet can go.
まだ行ってない人、 みんな行けるよ
I think I'll try this.
これでやってみようかな
I'm not going anymore.
もう行かない
It's like the phone is flopping.
電話ドボドボみたい
do?
やる?
Oh, I'm going in, I'm going in.
あー、入っちゃう、入っちゃう
I'll be right in, look.
すぐ入っちゃうよ、ほら見て
terrible.
やばい
It's already pecho pecho today.
もう今日ペチョペチョ
I have a very strong sexual desire, but I only have a strong sexual desire.
性欲強すぎなんですけど、性欲ばかり強いよ
I wouldn't do something like this unless I was strong.
強くないとやらないよ、こんなこと
I really like being seen.
見られるのめっちゃ好きだもん
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ちなさい
Wait a moment.
ちょっと 待ちなさい
I'll also add forgiveness.
容赦も追加しまーす
I was so fucked up.
めっちゃズボってった
I'll call you again, just for a while.
電話また入れちゃうよ、ちょっとずっと
good?
いい?
Put it in.
入れて
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Look, it's in.
ほ ら見て、入ってる
I want to continue without stopping until 10 o'clock.
このまま10時までノーストップで行きたいな
copper?
どう?
I'll be going all the way until 10 o'clock.
10時までずっと行きまくる
I want to try it.
やってやりたいな
There's also anal.
アナルもいるよ
It's like an endurance race.
耐久レースみたいになってる
Wait a minute, I have ears.
ちょっと待って、耳がついてる
I'm going to put it in my anus.
アナル入れちゃうよ
I'm in.
入っちゃったよ
I can't help it because it's so loud,
くちくちってうるさいからしょうがないから、
I'll show you my mouth.
口見せてあげるよ
Will I fit in?
入るかな?
Eh, can I do it like this?
え、こうやっていい?
If you blow your legs too much, you'll get leg cramps.
足を吹きすぎたら足つる
I felt like I was dehydrated and my legs got crampy.
脱水みたいになったら足つってきた
First of all, it's a demon.
まずして、鬼じゃん
Impossible.
無理
It gets stuck in your finger.
指につって入ったりする
I'll come in.
入るよ
Look.
ほ ら
Enter with plenty of time.
余裕で入る
I can't pee anymore.
もうおしっこ出ない
I'm seriously going to die.
マジで死ぬ
Okay.
よ いしょ
Do you understand?
わかるかな?
My body is covered in pee right now.
私の体がさ、今、めちゃめちゃおしっこまみれなの
appear?
見える?
Around here.
この辺とかは
Even my stomach was soaked.
お腹とかまでびっしょびしょなんだけど
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくない?
No, it's harsh.
いや、えぐい
I feel like I got really excited today.
今日めちゃめちゃカコイチ吹いた気がする
How was it?
どうでしたか?
It was amazing.
すごかったよね
It blew really hard.
めっちゃ吹いたよね
Someone who has known Minami since the beginning.
みなみのこと、最初の方から知ってる人
How many times today?
今日何回目の?
I forgot, but even if it's someone I've known from the beginning.
忘れちゃったけど、最初の方から知ってる人でも
It was amazing.
すごかった
It was amazing, I guess.
すごかったよね、やっぱり
The bed.
ベッドが
This is terrible.
やばいよ、これは
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
My butt is all sticky.
お尻がべちゃべちゃ
It was amazing, seriously.
すごかったよね、マジで
Wait a minute, here's a comment.
ちょっと待って、コメントが
It was very well done.
大 変よくできました
thank you.
ありがとう
Today was amazing, wasn't it?
すごかったよね、今日
I want to clean it up at the end.
終わりに片付けてあげたい
It's actually a pee sheet, even though I don't have a dog.
ほ んとおしっこのシートがさ、犬とか飼ってないのにさ
Because this is what happens.
こんなことになるからさ
It was amazing.
すごかった
Isn't it amazing?
すごいでしょ?
Really praise me.
ほんと褒めて
The anal was amazing too.
アナルもすごかった
thank you.
ありがとう
I'll do it, thank you.
やっておきますね、ありがとう
I'm happy.
嬉しいよ
When will the world come?
世界はいつ来てくれる?
Maybe next week, sometime on weekdays.
来週になるかな、平日のどっかかな
Stand up and show me your cracks.
立って割れ目見せて
crack.
割れ目
butt cuppa
お尻クパ
hmm.
ン
That's sad, Minami-chan.
さ しいな、みなみちゃん
real?
ほんと?
Who?
誰様?
Do you grow fluff?
毛羽伸ばすの?
What should I do with my hair?
毛どうしようかな?
I'm lost.
迷ってる
Honesty.
正直
I'm not particularly picky, so
別に私はこだわりそんなないから、
Either one is fine.
どっちでもいいんだけど
I feel like anything other than a stick would be fine.
なんか棒棒以外だったら何でもいいかなって感じ
Your ass was amazing today, really?
今日のお尻最高やった、ほんと?
thank you.
ありがとう
My legs are really cramping.
足がつる、ガチで
I can sleep well today, that's true.
今日はねっくり寝れるね、ほんとだよ
It was a mess.
めちゃめちゃいったもん
Just be careful.
ちょっと気をつけして
Be careful.
気をつけ
When is the next time?
次回はいつ頃かな?
next week.
来週
It's seriously hydrating.
マジで水分とるね
I drank all the tea though.
お茶全部飲んじゃったんだけどさ
Can it be heart-shaped?
ハート型ってできんの?
I don't know.
わかんない
Chin mask bread.
アゴマスクパン
Forcibly.
無理に
I messed up a while ago.
さっきめっちゃしたもん
I've been showing my face for a while now.
さっきから顔めっちゃ見せてるわ
Should we all save up some salt?
みんな塩を溜めとけばよかったかな?
There's about four bed sheets worth of salt in there.
そこにね、ベッドシーツ4枚分ぐらいの私の塩があるよ
Anyone who wants it, please.
欲しい人どうぞ
Please come and get it.
取りに来てください
Show me your butt while sitting like a Yankee.
ヤンキー座りでお尻見せて
Yankee sitting.
ヤンキー座りで
Butt.
お尻
like this?
こう?
Is this okay?
これで いいのかね?
Let's drink tea.
お茶飲もう
I drank it all.
全部飲んじゃったぜ
Well, I'm going to take a shower soon.
じゃあそろそろ私もシャワー浴びてきます